<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MRSCI on Mystical Rose School of Caloocan</title>
    <link>https://www.mysticalroseschoolofcaloocan.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MRSCI on Mystical Rose School of Caloocan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 20:43:50 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.mysticalroseschoolofcaloocan.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Core Values</title>
      <link>https://www.mysticalroseschoolofcaloocan.com/post/core-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 20:43:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mysticalroseschoolofcaloocan.com/post/core-values/</guid>
      <description>HuMility: We acknowledge and celebrate each of our achievements, keeping both feet on the ground, We know that each one of us have strengths and limitations.
CReativity: We accept change as an opportunity; we challenge conventional thinking and implement new ideas.
ReSpect: We practice fair judgment and we act responsibly mindful of other&amp;rsquo;s feelings.
ExCellence: We all share the responsibility to give the best that we can in everything that we do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>https://www.mysticalroseschoolofcaloocan.com/post/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 20:43:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mysticalroseschoolofcaloocan.com/post/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Pilosopo of the School:
Every student is different in the color of his personality, it is manifested in his own individuality. Because he is unique and vastly different from others he has his own way of development. Using the premise, the school aims to continuously nurture his development through the provision of enriching learning activities inside and outside the classroom, meaningful educational materials/facilities that suit his needs, and employment of well-trained teachers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vision</title>
      <link>https://www.mysticalroseschoolofcaloocan.com/post/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 20:42:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mysticalroseschoolofcaloocan.com/post/vision/</guid>
      <description>The Institution of Basic and Skills-based education in Caloocan that meets global framework of excellence, producing humane and holistic forerunners of the 2st century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission</title>
      <link>https://www.mysticalroseschoolofcaloocan.com/post/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 20:42:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mysticalroseschoolofcaloocan.com/post/mission/</guid>
      <description>Mystical Rose School is committed to produce globally competitive and socially responsive graduates honed through innovative teaching, learner-centered schooling, skills-focused training, life-long learning and safe and sound learning environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.mysticalroseschoolofcaloocan.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mysticalroseschoolofcaloocan.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>This is an example of a custom shortcode that you can put right into your content. You will need to add a form action to the the shortcode to make it work. Check out Formspree for a simple, free form service.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>